A Guide to the Thomas H. Hunter Collection 1934-1995
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPINGS 1967-1968, 7 Newsclippings (Box-folder 81-39)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1968, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 81-40)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS 1974-1975, 8 Newsletters (Box-folder 81-41)
- MISCELLANEOUS ENVELOPES (COMMEMORATIVE) AND REPRINT 1967/ca, 6 Envelopes With Stamps, Reprint (Box-folder 81-42)
- COMMITTEE REPORT 1974/ca, TMs (P) (Box-folder 82-1)
  UVA Self-Study Committee 1964 - 1974
- NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., AMs (Box-folder 82-2)
  UVA Self Study (Goals) Coordinating Committee
- F.E. DREIFUSS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973/02/23, TLS (Box-folder 82-3)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973, 6 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 82-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1972-1973, 7 TMs (P) (Box-folder 82-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINT N.D., Reprint (Box-folder 82-6)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1971-1976, TM (CC), TL (CC) (Box-folder 82-7)
  UVA Senate
- EUGENE FOSTER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1971/01/25, TLS (Box-folder 82-8)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970-1976, 29 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 82-9)
- POLICIES AND PROCEDURES STATEMENTS 1972-1979, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 82-10)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1970-1976, 20 TMs (P) (Box-folder 82-11)
- FRANK L. HEREFORD JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969/02/03, TLS (Box-folder 82-12)
  UVA Sesquicentennial Associate Selection Committee
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968-1970, 5 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 82-13)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO FRANLK BERKELEY 1969/12/18, TL (CC) (Box-folder 82-14)
  UVA Seven Society
- FRANCIS L. BERKELEY JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1970/01/05, TLS (Box-folder 82-15)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1970, 11 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 82-16)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1966-1971, 16 TL (CC) (Box-folder 82-17)
  UVA President Edgar F. Shannon, Jr. - 1966
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1974, 19 TLS, 4 TM (Box-folder 82-18)
- NOTE IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., AN (Box-folder 82-19)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1964-1967, 50 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 82-20)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1967-1970, 43 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 82-21)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1966-1970, 6 TMs (P) (Box-folder 82-22)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VINCENT SHEA 1966/02/28, TL (CC) (Box-folder 83-1)
  UVA Comptroller, A. Vincent Shea
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1970, TM, TLS (Box-folder 83-2)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1968-1969/ca, AN, AN (P) (Box-folder 83-3)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1969, 8 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 83-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL AND NOTE 1969/ca, AN, TMs (P) (Box-folder 83-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1969, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 83-6)
  UVA Director of Medical Center, John Stacey
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1969, 6 TLS (Box-folder 83-7)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1966-1971, 83 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 83-8)
- GOSPEL HILL -- GOAL 2 COMPLIANCE 1969, TMs (P), AN (Box-folder 83-9)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1973-1974, 2 TLS (P) (Box-folder 83-10)
  UVA Student Health
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1970-1972, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 83-11)
  UVA University Liaison Committee with Federal Executive Institute
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1973, 10 TLS (Box-folder 83-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., TN (Box-folder 83-13)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1971, 12 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 83-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969-1972, 8 TMs (P) (Box-folder 83-15)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS, PAMPHLETS, NEWSLETTERS 1969-1972, 13 Reprints/Pamphlets/Newsletters (Box-folder 83-16)
- PAUL SAUNIER JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1970, TM, 2 TLS (Box-folder 83-17)
  UVA University Relations Paul Saunier
- PAUL SAUNIER JR. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., TN (Box-folder 83-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLET AND POSTCARD 1975, Pamphlet, PC (Box-folder 83-19)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1969-1975, 13 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 83-20)
- EQUAL OPPORTUNITY AT THE UNIVERSITY OF VIRGINIA 1969/02/21, TMs (P) (Box-folder 83-21)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1968, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 83-22)
  UVA Upgrading of Salaries
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968, 3 TLS (Box-folder 83-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., AN (Box-folder 83-24)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPING 1969, Newsclipping (P) (Box-folder 83-25)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1968-1969, 16 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 83-26)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1969, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 83-27)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1962-1963, 50 TL ((C) (Box-folder 83-28)
  UVA
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 61 TLS (Box-folder 83-29)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, 11 ALS (Box-folder 83-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE AND CARD N.D., AN, Printed Card (Box-folder 83-31)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSLETTERS AND NEWSCLIPPINGS 1962, 4 Newsletters/Newsclippings (Box-folder 83-32)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1962-1963, AN, 11 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 83-33)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1962-1963, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 83-34)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945, TL (CC), Telegram (CC) (Box-folder 84-1)
  Personal Correspondence 1945-1947 A
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 7 TM, 14 TLS (Box-folder 84-2)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946-1947, 4 AM, 5 ALS (Box-folder 84-3)
- NOTES IN THOMAS H. HUNTER'S HAND N.D., 3 AN (Box-folder 84-4)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 A
- MEMO AND CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946, 2 TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 84-5)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1944-1947, 9 TMs (P) (Box-folder 84-6)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1945-1948, 10 Reprints (Box-folder 84-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS RECEIPTS 1945-1947, 8 Printed Forms (Box-folder 84-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENTS AND PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE 1945-1947/CA, 4 Printed Cards, 2 Photographs, B&W, 8x10 (Box-folder 84-9)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1944-1947, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-10)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 B
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1944-1947, 10 TLS (Box-folder 84-11)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946, Printed Card, ALS (Box-folder 84-12)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND ENVELOPE 1946/CA, 5 Pamphlets, Envelope (Box-folder 84-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENTS 1945-1946, 3 Printed Cards (Box-folder 84-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES 1946/01/16, AN (Box-folder 84-15)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 5 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-16)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 C
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 8 TLS (Box-folder 84-17)
- MISCELLANEOUS RECEIPTS AND NOTE 1945-1947/CA, AN, 9 Printed Forms (Box-folder 84-18)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENTS AND PHOTOGRAPH 1945-1947/CA, 5 Printed Cards, Photograph, B&W, 3x4.5 (Box-folder 84-19)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/06/21, TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 5 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-21)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 D
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1946, 2 TLS (Box-folder 84-22)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENT N.D., Printed Card (Box-folder 84-23)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1945/04/18, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 84-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 10 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-25)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 E, F
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 8 TLS (Box-folder 84-26)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946-1947, AN, 3 ALS (Box-folder 84-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARD AND RECEIPTS 1947, PC, 8 Printed Forms (Box-folder 84-28)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENTS AND PHOTOGRAPUBLIC HEALTH SERVICE 1945-1947/CA, 4 Printed Cards, 5 Photographs, B&W, 3.25x4.5 (Box-folder 84-29)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-30)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 G
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 5 TLS (Box-folder 84-31)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1944-1945, 2 ALS (Box-folder 84-32)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMO 1945/05/11, TM (Box-folder 84-33)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1946-1947, 6 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-34)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 H, I, J
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946-1947, 6 TLS (Box-folder 84-35)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMO 1946/11/18, AM (Box-folder 84-36)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMOS AND RECEIPT 1945-1946, 4 TM, Printed Form (Box-folder 84-37)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENTS N.D., 3 Printed Cards, Envelope (Box-folder 84-38)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946/09/20, TLS (Box-folder 84-39)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1946-1947, 15 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-40)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 K, L
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946-1947, 9 TLS (Box-folder 84-41)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, TM, 10 AM, 4 ALS (Box-folder 84-42)
- LAIRD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/08/11, Telegram (Box-folder 84-43)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTE N.D., AN (Box-folder 84-44)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/07/11, ALS (Box-folder 84-45)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1944/CA, 3 TMs (P) (Box-folder 84-46)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENT AND MEMOS 1945-1947, TM Printed Card, Printed Form (Box-folder 84-47)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 12 TL (CC), TN (CC) (Box-folder 84-48)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 M
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 16 TLS (Box-folder 84-49)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 2 ALS (Box-folder 84-50)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARDS, ANNOUNCEMENT, RECEIPTS 1945-1947/CA, 2 PC, Printed Card, 10 Printed Forms (Box-folder 84-51)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS N.D., 2 Telegrams (CC) (Box-folder 84-52)
  PERSONAL CORRESPENDENCE, 1945-1947 M
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946/02/27, TLS (Box-folder 84-53)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1945/CA, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 84-54)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1946-1947, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-55)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 N, O
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946-1947, 7 TLS (Box-folder 84-56)
- A. F. OVERSTREET TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 84-57)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARDS AND RECEIPTS 1946, 2 PC, 2 Printed Forms (Box-folder 84-58)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCIPT MATERIAL 1945-1947/CA, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 84-59)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-60)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 P, Q
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 13 TLS (Box-folder 84-61)
- SYDNEY L. [ ] TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946/07/05, ALS (Box-folder 84-62)
- MISCELLANEOUS NOTES N.D., AN (Box-folder 84-63)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENTS AND RECEIPTS 1945-1946, GG Printed Forms, 2 Printed Cards (Box-folder 84-64)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946-1947, 17 TLS/TL/TM (P) (Box-folder 84-65)
- PENICILLIN N.D., TMs (CC) (Box-folder 84-66)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1946, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 84-67)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 R
- ISADORE RUDNIKOFF TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1946/10/02, TLS (Box-folder 84-68)
- RONNY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 84-69)
- RECEIPT 1946/03/01, Printed Form (Box-folder 84-70)
  PERSONAL CORRESONDENCE, 1945-1947 R
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-1)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 S
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1944-1947, 12 TLS (Box-folder 85-2)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/06/17, TLS (Box-folder 85-3)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1947/CA, 2 TMs (CC) (Box-folder 85-4)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMOS, NOTES, ANNOUNCEMENTS 1945/CA, 2 TM, 2 AN, 3 Printed Cards (Box-folder 85-5)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1945-1947, 7 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-6)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 T, U, V
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1946, 6 TLS (Box-folder 85-7)
- MISCELLANEOUS APPLICATIONS 1945/CA, 3 Printed Forms (Box-folder 85-8)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLET AND ANNOUNCEMENT 1946/CA, Pamphlet, Printed Card (Box-folder 85-9)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 946-1947, 16 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-10)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 W
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1945-1947, 23 TLS (Box-folder 85-11)
- BOB [GLASER] TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 85-12)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO WILLIAM A. WERRELL N.D., Telegram (CC) (Box-folder 85-13)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS AND ANNOUNCEMENT 1947/CA, 2 Pamphlets, Printed Card (Box-folder 85-14)
- MISCELLANEOUS POSTCARD, V-MAIL LETTER, RECEIPTS 1945-1947, PC, AL, 5 Printed Forms (Box-folder 85-15)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO GORDON ZUBROD 1947/09/05, TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-16)
  Personal Correspondence, 1945-1947 Y, Z
- GODON ZUBROD TO THOMAS H. HUNTER [1947]/08/31, ALS (Box-folder 85-17)
- YORKE PUBLISHING CO. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/05/01, TLS (Box-folder 85-18)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 18 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-19)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 A
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 16 TLS (Box-folder 85-20)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/05/04, TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-21)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY AND LEASE SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/08/27, TLS (P), TMs (P) (Box-folder 85-22)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 27 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-23)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 B
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 12 TLS (Box-folder 85-24)
- RUDY TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/12/13, ALS (Box-folder 85-25)
- HARRY S. BERNTON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/03/22, Telegram (Box-folder 85-26)
- MISCELLANEOUS PAMPHLETS, RECEIPTS, ANNOUNCEMENT 1948/CA, 2 Printed Forms, 2 Pamphlets, Printed Card (Box-folder 85-27)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 14 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-28)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 C
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 14 TLS (Box-folder 85-29)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 4 ALS (Box-folder 85-30)
- MISCELLANEOUS APPLICATIONS AND MEMOS 1948/CA, 2 Printed Forms, TM (Box-folder 85-31)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 4 TLS/TL (P) (Box-folder 85-32)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER'S CV AND REPRINT LIST 1948/CA, 2 TMs, 6 TMs (CC) (Box-folder 85-33)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1949, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-34)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 D
- ABBIE KNOWLTON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/01/19, TLS (Box-folder 85-35)
  PERSONAL CRRESPONDENCE, 1948 D
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 3 ALS (Box-folder 85-36)
- RECEIPT 1948/CA, Printed Form (Box-folder 85-37)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 E
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 14 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-38)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 F
- VAIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 5 TLS (Box-folder 85-39)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 5 ALS (Box-folder 85-40)
- MEMOS SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 2 TM (P) (Box-folder 85-41)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 7 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-42)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 G
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 4 TLS (Box-folder 85-43)
- MARJORIE [P. GREGORY] TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 4 ALS (Box-folder 85-44)
- RECEIPT 1948/06/10, Printed Form (Box-folder 85-45)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 17 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-46)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 H
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, MEDICAL LICENSE 1947-1948, 3 TLS, Certificate (Box-folder 85-47)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 5 ALS (Box-folder 85-48)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIALS 1948, TMs, TMs (P) (Box-folder 85-49)
- CHARLES T. BOHLE CO. TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/06/25, TLS (Box-folder 85-50)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 I
- INSURANCE MATERIALS 1948, 6 Printed Forms, Printed Card (Box-folder 85-51)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-52)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 K
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 5 TLS (Box-folder 85-53)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1948/05, TMs (CC) (Box-folder 85-54)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 10 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-55)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 L
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 5 TLS (Box-folder 85-56)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 2 ALS (Box-folder 85-57)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1949, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-58)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 M
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 4 TLS (Box-folder 85-59)
- WILLIAM MCLAUGHLIN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/10/26, ALS (Box-folder 85-60)
- MISCELLANEOUS ANNOUNCEMENT 1948/CA, Printed Card (Box-folder 85-61)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-62)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 N
- B. WALLACE HAMILTON TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/02/10, TLS (Box-folder 85-63)
  Personal Correspondence, 148 N
- E. STERLING NICHOL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/05/19, TPCS (Box-folder 85-64)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-65)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 O
- H. G. OGDEN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/08/13, APCS (Box-folder 85-66)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 20 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-67)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 P
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 16 TLS (Box-folder 85-68)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 3 ALS (Box-folder 85-69)
- BILL PYLES TO THOMAS H. HUNTER, MISCELLANEOUS NOTE 1947-1948, AN, TPCS (Box-folder 85-70)
- MEMO AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 3 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 85-71)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1949, 11 TL (CC) (Box-folder 85-72)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 R
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 6 TLS (Box-folder 85-73)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 3 ALS (Box-folder 85-74)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, TLS, 22 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-1)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 S
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 12 TLS (Box-folder 86-2)
- ERNIE SACHS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947/09/24, ALS (Box-folder 86-3)
- CORRESPONDENCE COPY SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/04/27, TLS (Box-folder 86-4)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 7 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-5)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 T
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1948, 4 TLS (Box-folder 86-6)
- MAULIO JOHN TERRAGNI TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947, 3 ALS (Box-folder 86-7)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1948, TLS, 4 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-8)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 U, V
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1949, 5 TLS (Box-folder 86-9)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL 1948, 2 TMs (P) (Box-folder 86-10)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1947-1948, 19 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-11)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 W
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1947-1949, 12 TLS, TN (Box-folder 86-12)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1948, 3 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-13)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 X, Y
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948, 2 TLS (Box-folder 86-14)
- INSURANCE FORM 1948/02/11, Printed Form (Box-folder 86-15)
- ROBERT M. ZOLLINGER TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948/11/24, TLS (Box-folder 86-16)
  Personal Correspondence, 1948 Z
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-17)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 A
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948-1950, 5 TLS (Box-folder 86-18)
- MEMOS AND CORRESPONDENCE COPIES SENT TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 4 TLS/TM (P) (Box-folder 86-19)
- MEETING SCHEDULE 1950/03/17, Pamphlet (Box-folder 86-20)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949, 11 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-21)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 B
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 5 TLS (Box-folder 86-22)
- C. R. B. BLACKBURN TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949/03/24, ALS (Box-folder 86-23)
- TELEGRAM COPY AND COPY OF THOMAS H. HUNTER'S BIRTH CERTIFICATE 1949, TM, Printed Form (P) (Box-folder 86-24)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 15 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-25)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 C
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 6 TLS (Box-folder 86-26)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 3 ALS (Box-folder 86-27)
- MISCELLANEOUS REPRINTS 1946-1949, 3 Reprints (Box-folder 86-28)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL [1936]-1950, 5 TMs (P) (Box-folder 86-29)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 17 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-30)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 D
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1948-1949, 9 TLS (Box-folder 86-31)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 4 ALS (Box-folder 86-32)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1950, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-33)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 E, F
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 5 TLS (Box-folder 86-34)
- EVELYN S. FELL TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1950/04/07, ALS (Box-folder 86-35)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 2 TMS (Box-folder 86-36)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 8 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-37)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 G
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 2 TLS (Box-folder 86-38)
- MARJORIE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949/01/26, ALS (Box-folder 86-39)
- MISCELLANEOUS RECEIPTS 1949, 3 Printed Forms (Box-folder 86-40)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 16 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-41)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 H, I, J
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 17 TLS (Box-folder 86-42)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 3 ALS (Box-folder 86-43)
- MISCELLANEOUS INCOME TAX AND OTHER FORMS 1949-1950, 26 Printed Forms (Box-folder 86-44)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPT MATERIAL RE JESSIE HUNTER 1949, TMs (P) (Box-folder 86-45)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 12 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-46)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 K, L
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 9 TLS (Box-folder 86-47)
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 2 ALS (Box-folder 86-48)
- MISCELLANEOUS NEWSCLIPPING N.D., Newsclipping (Box-folder 86-49)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 9 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-50)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 M
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 7 TLS (Box-folder 86-51)
- MISCELLANEOUS MANUSCRIPTS BY THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949/CA, TMs, 2 TMs (CC) (Box-folder 86-52)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949, 2 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-53)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 N, O
- ELIZABETH CRADDICK TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949, 2 TLS (Box-folder 86-54)
- VICTOR NAJJAR TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949/05/17, ALS (Box-folder 86-55)
- MISCELLANEOUS MEMO AND NARCOTICS INVENTORY 1949, TM (P) Printed Form (Box-folder 86-56)
- THOMAS H. HUNTER TO VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS 1949-1950, 12 TL (CC) (Box-folder 86-57)
  Personal Correspondence, 1949 P, Q
- VARIOUS CORRESPONDENTS TO THOMAS H. HUNTER 1949-1950, 11 TLS (Box-folder 86-58)
- KENNETH PAYNE TO THOMAS H. HUNTER N.D., ALS (Box-folder 86-59)